- Yeah, yeah.
- Okay, got it?
- Saotome.
- Saotome?
- Moon radical, then five, then woman.
- Yeah.
- It's Saotome.
- So it's Saotomezaka.
- Saotome.
- And...
- Right.
- Bangkok's official name...
- Krung Thep.
- Huh? Plung?
- Krung Thep?
- Thep.
- Thep. - Yeah.
- Maha Nakhon.
- Ma-Maha-na?
- Maha-na.
- Maha Nakhon.
- Khon.
- Amon.
- Rattana.
- Yeah.
- Kosin.
- Huh? What was it?
- Hoshin?
- Ko.
- K-o, like ka-ki-ku-ke-ko.
- Oh, ko.
- Kosin.
- Mahinta.
- Mahinta?
- Yeah.
- Rayutthaya.
- Yuttara.
- Yutthaya.
- Yeah.
- Mahadilok.
- Mahadi, Mahadi.
- Maha.
- Stretch it out.
- Mahadilok.
- Yeah.
- Pop.
- Nopparat.
- This is like a Saraba skit.
- It's like one of those rip-off bars.
- This is exactly like a rip-off bar.
- Nop...
- Huh.
- Nopparat.
- Yeah.
- Right.
- Ratchathani.
- Wait, uh, Ratchathani.
- Ratcha.
- Ratchathani.
- Stretch it out, right.
- And then Burirom.
- Bu-Buri.
- Burirom.
- Rom.
- Rom, right.
- Is that it?
- Uh, we're only halfway.
- Halfway!?
- I'm hungry.
- Oh, we're actually getting somewhere.
- It's going.
- I want some chocolate.
- Yeah, I do want chocolate.
- Whoa!
- Damn, I'm losing it.
- I'm done, man.
- So that's what happens when you hit your
limit.
- Exactly.
- Yeah, I can see myself snapping.
- You really do lose it when you hit your
limit.
- It all hits you at once.
- What was it? Maha?
- Maha-na.
- Hey, someone answer the phone.
- The phone, the phone, the phone, for
now.
- Wait.
- For now, do we know anybody's number?
- Can't we just use LINE?
- No, LINE won't work.
- Right.
- You need it now?
- What else did we look up? What else was
there?
- Former prime ministers.
- Former...
- It already hung up.
- You're too damn loud.
- We only got halfway through Thailand.
- We're not getting anywhere.
- This sucks.
- No, we're still only halfway.
- Look, if we can't do it, then that's
that.
- We already know this one.
- Then we've gotta go there.
- Then go for this one first.
- This Saotomezaka one.
- This one.
- Saotomezaka.
- Do we press it?
- How do we do this?
- Oh!
- Isn't this good? Isn't this good?
- Huh?
- What?
- It worked!
- What does that mean?
- Hell yeah!
- Ohh, so that's it!
- Oh!
- I get it!
- Then it's gotta be around here!
- So we just need to go around here!
- Yeah.
- So we don't have to open all of them.
- Can you see it?
- Man, this is scary as hell.
- Like...
- What I can see is...
- a ruin.
- I can barely see anything.
- Even if we got out...
- Yeah.
- it still feels like we wouldn't make it.
- Seriously.
- Is there acrylic over this? Look.
- There's no cover on it.
- No cover?
- Just barely?
- This front one's the closest.
- I'm going in.
- I don't think it's bad.
- Got it! - Something went in! It went in!
It went in!
- Got it!
- It's all the way in!
- No, this is bad.
- My grip's weak.
- We just blew a million.
- What?
- A million.
- This is bad.
- Wait, no, this is bad. This is bad.
- A million disappears fast.
- This...
- Who came up with this whole idea?
- Seriously, are they insane?
- Knock it off.
- I don't even know where the line is
anymore.
- This is the kind of thing a madman comes
up with.
- We're not even talking like this is
gonna air anymore.
- They're asking stuff they know we can't
do.
- What is this? I don't even know.
- They didn't simulate this, did they?
- Yeah.
- Wait a second.
- Ah, wait a second.
- Huh?
- It's going up!
- 100, 1,000, 10,000, 100,000, 100.
- This is a total mess.
- This is the worst.
- See?
- What?
- So that's how it works.
- Ugh, this is the worst.
- No, this is bad.
- This is bad.
- Bad.
- What?
- Damn, it went up way too much.
- No, wait.
- Maybe you're not supposed to buy it
every time?
- How far do we go with this?
- If we open these three, we can do it,
right?
- I think we can.
- Yeah.
- We can do it, we can do it.
- We should go for Thailand after all.
- For now, let's just buy it.
- We're already halfway through.
- It's a million yen.
- No, the next part's scary.
- See?
- Down, down.
- Ah.
- This part's crazy.
- We just need to drop it in here.
- Ah.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Who is it?
- Harumi Nemoto again.
- They're piling up.
- Why?
- Signed, too.
- This might actually be pretty rare.
- From back when she still had that
miraculous sparkle in her eyes.
- Harumi Nemoto.
- I see.
- So what are we supposed to do with this
one?
- Last time...
- Google actually talked to us before,
didn't it?
- Yeah.
- Just to kill time, just to kill time.
- Okay, Google.
- Tell us something funny.
- How about this?
- Do you know who's the most stylish
person on an airplane?
- Huh?
- Who?
- Oh?
- The copilot.
- Because... it's a wordplay thing.
- Ah.
- Oh.
- Sounds like a rakugo storyteller.
- Weren't there riddles too?
- Okay, Google.
- Give us a riddle.
- Sure. How about this riddle?
- Mm-hm.
- A new car is called brand-new. So what
do you call a car that's about to break down?
- Zenigata?
- Think about the answer now.
- It's totally gatagata.
- Wait, isn't it gatagata? Uh...
- Oh, rattly! Rattly!
- Now, your answer please.
- Gata-gata!
- Correct. The answer is gata-gata.
- Okay!
- What have you been doing this whole
time?
- But we won.
- Oh, that's funny.
- Okay Google, since we got it right, do
we win anything?
- Sorry. I have nothing prepared.
- Then give us something!
- We're really bullying Google now.
- Isn't this basically the escape plan
now?
- Isn't this how we get out?
- Your brain's still working.
- Yeah.
- Yeah. Ah, sorry. So...
- More than the phone number...
- Yeah.
- Could you blast out a LINE message to a
few people?
- Huh? Why?
- To whoever can actually move.
- Ah, okay.
- Okay, I'll tell you now.
- So this is mission control now?
- Today.
- Tokyo District Court.
- Yeah, and the trials being held...
- Being held...
- Out of those trials...
- This might be rough.
- Yeah.
- One courtroom name.
- Ah, we have to go there in person.
- We have to go there.
- The defendant.
- Give the judgment.
- No, it'll be happening when they get
there.
- Right, any one is fine.
- Just go get one that's actually in
session.
- One that's happening right then.
- Just have them look.
- They'd have to sit in on it.
- Right, right, right.
- Then have them tell us the result.
And...
- Man, that's ten coins already.
- Gotanda Queens.
- Akari-chan.
- Answer what color her panties are today.
- It's probably a brothel, honestly.
- Ah.
- Yeah, we'll pay the money, so...
- I see.
- They don't have to do anything, just
check the panty color and come right back.
- Yeah.
- Got it.
- And tell them this too, just in case.
- The Hibiya Park fountain's...
- Give today's water temperature.
- Blast these three out to anyone who can
do them.
- Damn, we've already spent a ton.
- And first, that thing we asked about.
- The common point among those prime
ministers.
- That prime minister one is rough.
- I can't figure it out.
- No idea.
- Why?
- It's not coming up.
- Huh? Even when I type it in, nothing
comes up.
- Say the names one more time.
- You said them too fast before.
- Abe, Koizumi, Obuchi.
- Who else was it?
- Miyazawa.
- Miki, Hatoyama.
- Hiranuma, Hayashi.
- Hiranuma.
- Hayashi.
- So call again. We should call again.
- Okay, I'll hang up once.
- Yeah, okay.
- Check that prime minister one again too.
- Okay, hang on. I'm calling now.
- Okay.
- No, I mean...
- That's already a lot.
- No, I already went. We used 26.
- And we still haven't learned anything.
Seriously.
- Ugh.
- Well, anyway, next.
- Let's ask around for one we can do.
- And...
- Bangkok.
- Yeah, we should go with that one.
- We should. If we don't, we can't open
it.
- Since we've come this far, we should go
for it.
- So, for now...
- Wait a bit?
- Okay, we tested this with one million.
- Then with this other million, let's see
how much we can raise over here.
- Right, right.
- Then let's think in terms of eight
million.
- Okay. Where does the eight million go?
- I think that's a really good idea.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- Please.
- One million. - Okay, let's start with
rock-paper-scissors.
- Yeah.
- Right, this thing.
- Hit Start, and I think it goes
rock-paper-scissors, shoot.
- First, put in one medal.
- This is luck too, though.
- Rock, paper, scissors.
- Damn.
- Tie.
- We won, we won.
- We won? - No way.
- We won.
- Medal, okay.
- Oh, two came out, they did, they did.
- Two.
- Twenty grand.
- Ten became twenty.
- Damn.
- Amazing.
- It's baccarat.
- Damn.
- Two, four, eight... no, four, eight,
sixteen, thirty-two.
- Oh, it doubles each time.
- I see.
- Ah.
- So maybe we weren't supposed to return
the medal.
- The winning one.
- Yeah.
- Rock, paper, scissors... za, za.
- Nice.
- Oh, we won, we won, we won.
- It's at two now. - Two.
- Ah.
- So we just do this again, right?
- Let's hit Start.
- Oh, you're right.
- Pon, nice.
- Oh, wow.
- It went to four.
- What do we do?
- Damn, damn, ten grand turned into forty
grand.
- Going again is wild.
- Za, za.
- Tie.
- Tie, za.
- Whoa.
- Hey, what are you doing?
- Yeah.
- At least tell me if you're going for it.
- Like, whether you're going or not.
- Yeah.
- This part worries me.
- My hands are sweating.
- This... wait, what do we do here?
- Ah.
- Number big?
- All right.
- Sorry, Sanshiro.
- Whoa, big one.
- Sorry.
- Are you seriously about to take a dump?
- No, make it just pee.
- Ugh.
- It looks huge too, ugh, this is...
- Sorry.
- Gross.
- I'm so sorry.
- No, ugh...
- Ugh.
- Please stop.
- This is hell.
- This is literally hell.
- What are you doing?
- I hate this.
- How can you even do that?
- How can you do it in here?
- Yeah.
- There's no way this is possible.
- Wait a second.
- Ugh, that's disgusting.
- No, this is disgusting.
- This is the worst.
- This place is rougher than prison.
- Ah, ah, sorry.
- Ah, turn the other way when you do it.
- Ah, sorry, it's coming out.
- Ugh, gross.
- Gross, sorry.
- Ugh.
- Ah, it came out.
- Sorry.
- Ugh.
- Ah, sorry.
- There's not even a bidet or anything.
- Right.
- I'm sorry.
- No, this seriously reeks.
- You're enjoying this now.
- I'm sorry.
- You're used to doing this in front of
people, right?
- This isn't your first time, is it?
- It started.
- It's started.
- Man, I want yakiniku. Or sushi.
- I want yakiniku. I want sushi too.
- I want sushi.
- This isn't a great sleeping position.
- This might be impossible.
- Can I seriously take a break for a sec?
- Maybe we should take a break.
- Otherwise I seriously won't last.
- I'm done. - Yeah.
- Space.
- No, I'm okay, just here...
- I'm going.
- No, this is scary, sleeping here.
- You should absolutely not do that.
- Should I lie down sideways?
- It's already shaking a lot.
- Wait.
- Ah, let it all out at once.
- Ah, more's coming out.
- So much is coming out.
- It's really pouring out.
- Ah.
- I want out of here already.
- What is this picture?
- Right next to somebody taking a dump.
- Wipe at the end, okay?
- Hurry up and wipe your ass.
- Sanshiro.
- I've never seen a composition like this.
- Oh.
- Lucky break.
- Nasty.
- Ugh.
- Lucky break.
- Nasty.
- You're enjoying this now.
- What the hell did you eat?
- What do you even eat to make that
happen?
- Peyang.
- Apologize to Peyang.
- A cup yakisoba record.
- I'm gonna go get some fresh air.
- Yeah.
- Fresh air.
- Want to make a call?
- Wait.
- What were we supposed to ask first
again?
- Ask about the court one.
- See who might be able to go.
- Kotetsu's trying hard to ask around.
- Okay.
- What about the court?
- Yeah. And when is it?
- Wait, me?
- No, did you find somebody?
- No, I still haven't been able to ask
yet.
- Yeah, ask that first.
- There are too many parts to it.
- Huh? You didn't ask?
- Ask that first.
- That one's scary. Morita's side is fine.
- I'll ask if they can help.
- Sandal?
- Yeah, yeah.
- So, uh, did we figure out the prime
minister one?
- We seriously don't know the prime
minister one.
- No idea. Seriously?
- It doesn't come up even online.
- It really doesn't come up.
- Doesn't come up. Yeah.
- I'll ask them to help.
- Don't say no right away.
- Don't we know someone? You know,
someone...
- Smart.
- Kotake Seigikan.
- Ah, Kotake Seigikan.
- Should we ask him then?
- Yeah, ask him.
- Kotake Seigikan. Maybe with him we
wouldn't even need to go to court.
- Kotake Seigikan doesn't know the court
one either.
- He's a lawyer, though.
- He probably knows how to look it up.
- Ask Kotake Seigikan about that prime
minister one too.
- Ask him that too.
- This is bad, bad.
- And bad.
- But let's open the Thailand one.
- Sure.
- Pick up where we left off on Thailand.
- Can we do Thailand?
- Thailand might be impossible right now,
no?
- We already said Niwet.
- Niwet.
- Maha Satan.
- Amon Piman.
- Amon.
- Piman.
- Sanukam.
- Huh? What?
- Sa.
- Nu.
- Huh? What?
- Why can't I hear you?
- Because you're saying it from the side.
- Over and over.
- We keep having this same exchange over
and over.
- Prasit.
- Pra.
- This is so kind of them.
- Sit.
- Sit, right.
- They've gone this far for us.
- Is Prasit the end?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- Okay, okay, okay.
- For now, the court one.
- The court.
- Anyone who can move on the court one.
- And if they can do the panties one too,
ask them.
- Yeah. - Okay, then maybe in twenty or
thirty minutes.
- Or anyway, we'll keep checking on our
end for anyone who can move.
- I'll call again.
- Got it.
- Okay, okay. Then please handle the prime
minister one.
- Okay, yeah.
- Okay.
- All right. We used a ton on that.
- So what happened in the end?
- For now, should we open Thailand?
- Assuming Thailand is right.
- Give Bangkok's full official name
without abbreviating it.
- Krung Thep Maha Nakhon Amon Rattanakosin
Mahinthara Yutthaya Mahadilok Pop Nopparat Ratchathani Burirom Udomratchaniwet Mahasathan Amon Piman Awatan Sathit Sakkathattiya Witsanukam Prasit.
- Press it.
- That's not it.
- Wrong.
- See? That's why I said there was risk
here.
- Yeah, maybe.
- Seriously?
- Because it didn't open, right?
- That's not it.
- I'm telling you, there's risk here.
That's what I've been saying.
- No, no, but this is hard enough just to
hear over the phone. - It is hard.
- That's what I'm saying. I think we
should give up on this one.
- How much have I spent on just this? Like
fifty already!
- No, but still...
- That won't work.
- But we have to open that one eventually.
- No, no, I'm saying...
- What do we do, give up on this?
- No, but both you and Gotetsu mumble too
much.
- No, no, on the phone you're too loud
too, right next to me.
- Then I'll listen. I will. I'll ask
Gotetsu myself.
- Sure, go ahead and ask.
- Yeah. But I still can't hear a thing.
- No, I don't know.
- But we only have eight left.
- Do you know how to do this?
- No. I've never done it, never even seen
it before.
- What is this?
- A Lamborghini.
- Press a number button each time you
insert a medal.
- Ah.
- Want to try once?
- Okay.
- So you place a bet.
- Put in one medal at a time.
- It went in.
- Then should we go purple?
- Huh, huh.
- Oh, so it lights up, and the question is
whether it stops there. - Right.
- Oh, it's spinning.
- This is hard.
- This is really hard.
- It just has to stop on purple.
- Ah, I get it. That's why the
multiplier's low.
- Ah, I get it. Got it.
- Going purple was really a long shot just
now.
- Ah.
- Right. There's only one slot for it.
- Right.
- Red is double, I guess.
- Yeah.
- Four times, six times.
- Ah, I get it, I get it. Okay, okay, got
it.
- Can't you place several at once here?
- Yeah.
- You can do that?
- You can?
- The medals.
- It says you can put up to four medals on
each number per medal inserted.
- One. - Then hit it and try putting one
in again.
- Oh, right.
- There.
- This really is gambling.
- Up until you hit Start.
- I see.
- And we've only used two medals so far.
- Six... ah, well, this could end fast,
though.
- It's really watching us.
- Try it once with these three.
- Okay.
- Yellow, green, and blue.
- If it lands on yellow, green, or blue,
we're good.
- Is it okay to use three?
- Come on.
- Red.
- Huh?
- That just burned three more.
- Red. - Damn, this thing's gonna swallow
us whole.
- Takano, you try it once. Try it once.
- This is straight-up betting, seriously.
- This would be fun if it were real money.
- Okano would've absolutely loved this.
He'd be losing his mind.
- You gamble at all?
- I don't.
- Right, same, I don't either.
- Figures they picked guys who don't
gamble for this.
- Maybe like this?
- Let's do orange, green, and blue too.
- Going blue.
- It's coming.
- Ah, but if blue hits, we'll get a lot
back.
- Yeah.
- Feels like yellow's coming.
- Yellow really feels like it's coming.
- By Murphy's law, it's gonna be yellow.
- Don't be yellow.
- Orange, green, blue.
- We've used thirty grand?
- We've used thirty grand.
- Yeah, we've used thirty grand.
- Hell yeah!
- Yes!
- How many?
- Man, you're really good at this.
- Maybe I am good at this.
- Got it.
- Four.
- Good, good, good, good.
- For now, we might've made it back.
- This is ten at a time.
- So we bet three more after that?
- Ah, it didn't go up that much.
- Just one.
- Right.
- We only gained one.
- Then we celebrated way too hard.
- There've gotta be kids whose lives got
ruined by finding this as children.
- No, wait a second.
- That dice one.
- I think it's six to the tenth power.
- And what is six to the tenth power?
- No, or maybe...
- The math is brutal.
- The one where it's six times six times
six times six...
- Not ten times?
- Wait, maybe we can do this.
- Can't we do that?
- No, we can.
- But if we mess up the math again, we're
back where we started.
- We'll just get irritated again.
- No, this might actually work.
- All right, here we go.
- Got it?
- We can do this.
- Wait, this might work.
- Can I go for it?
- I should just solve it myself.
- Uh...
- One in 21,586,176.
- Oh, how is it?
- Ah, if that's right, amazing.
- Wait, that's wrong.
- Ahh!
- Wrong, wrong, wrong.
- What!?
- Ah, it's shaking.
- Why does it suddenly shake out of
nowhere?
- Hey.
- Ah, but it stopped now.
- Yeah.
- Ah, the phone.
- Number one, once.
- You have to pick up.
- Okay.
- It's easy to grab because this place is
cramped.
- It is now meal time.
- Meal time?
- Please wait a moment while your meal is
prepared.
- What?
- What is it?
- It's like only the food is coming out.
- Why?
- Was that ringing just now?
- It rang, right?
- It did ring.
- Does that mean somebody can get through
on the phone?
- What's that supposed to mean?
- So far it's just there to scare us.
- What about the food?
- Oh, so we can ask for stuff? Like water?
- Oh, you think we can ask for it?
- Where would it even come out from?
- It's not like a door opens either.
- What's with that one-ring call thing?
- Isn't something in there? No, nothing.
- No, this one didn't open.
- Didn't open?
- You don't get it?
- Wait, is it this?
- Like, grab it during that one-ring call?
- Oh.
- That's a pretty low chance, though.
- Earlier.
- What was it again?
- Wasn't the first one like an hour ago?
- So that's it.
- Seriously?
- I'm seriously thirsty, though.
- Hey.
- Man, what do we do?
- Okay, Google. - Quit messing around. -
How long can a human survive without drinking water?
- Hurry it up.
- The Santani dot co dot jp website says
this:
- However, without taking even a drop of
water, a person can survive only four to five days at most.
- So we're still okay for now.
- Exactly.
- We can still keep going.
- Oh.
- Is it coming?
- It's coming.
- This is good for us.
- Whoa.
- Oh.
- Huh? Curry rice?
- Whoa.
- Right after someone took a dump? Worst
timing possible.
- It didn't go down by even one.
- One. - Give us supplies.
- Give us supplies.
- We need some energy.
- All right.
- Especially after seeing that.
- I'll have a little.
- Spicy.
- Eating curry that smells like shit is
rough.
- Absolutely not.
- Yeah.
- Man, sorry. - That's unrelated. - Yeah.
- Sharing curry like this is gross enough
already.
- Absolutely not.
- It's good, though.
- Tastes good.
- Mm.
- Why did they give us curry?
- It stinks.
- Maybe because someone took a dump.
- You're treating him like the main deity
now.
- Kind of...
- Doesn't it add to the other side?
- But if using the toilet makes food come
out...
- Inside the intestines...
- It's smoothing out the intestines.
- I hate alternating like this.
- He's really eating.
- Thanks for the meal.
- He's really putting it away. Seriously.
- No thanks.
- Wait, is this right?
- Well, we just have to try it.
- Let's go.
- One in 60,466,176.
- Please!
- Here we go.
- Oh!
- Come on, come on!
- It went!
- Yes!
- See!?
- Told you.
- See?
- But that means we got it wrong.
- Seriously.
- We're okay, right? Even the curve should
go if it's packed this tight.
- Please, go.
- Seriously, go.
- Oh, so it's already been thrown?
- We just need to give it a little push
and make it through here.
- If it doesn't fall now, that'll be the
worst. The worst.
- This spot, this one spot, seriously.
- This is tense.
- We only checked the big zone for now.
- Shall we do it?
- All right.
- Yes.
- Okay, okay, let's go.
- Okay, okay, okay.
- Here we go.
- Okay.
- Then once I press it, please take over
on your side.
- Okay.
- Here we go.
- Please, go.
- Dominoes, start.
- Good, good, good, good, good, good.
- Yes, yes, yes, please.
- Whoa.
- Over at Iguchi's part.
- Iguchi's part.
- Iguchi, what is that supposed to mean?
- Iguchi's section.
- No, not Iguchi's section exactly.
- Because that slope is Iguchi, right?
- No, seriously.
- No, I mean, if it's not going to be set
down normally, then what can we do?
- No, no, I mean it got here, but it still
didn't make it.
- You really say it straight.
- Nothing we can do about that.
- Right?
- That's what it is.
- Hey.
- We should at least be able to ask about
the prime ministers soon. We should have an answer soon, right?
- Yeah.
- Then ask Kotetsu.
- And what do we do about Thailand?
- Hmm, Thailand is impossible with the
remaining units.
- Yeah.
- Try saying it more clearly.
- Huh?
- What, what, what, what?
- What was that just now?
- There was something really scary just
now.
- It looked like some kind of executioner.
- Oh!
- An iron mask.
- What? - Whoa.
- What does that mean?
- Which side is that thing on?
- That's terrifying.
- Wait, which side is it on?
- Man, I wonder.
- That's terrifying.
- It was dressed like Jagi.
- Huh?
- What the hell?
- Damn, scary. If that thing comes out,
we're screwed.
- What does that mean?
- If something like that comes in here,
we're finished.
- Yeah.
- Makes you not want to get out, right?
- I don't know anymore.
- I want a cigarette!
- Cigarettes!
- Just let me smoke one cigarette, please.
- Please, give me a cigarette.
- A million is fine. I'll buy a cigarette
for a million.
- I'll buy one pack for a million yen.
- Please give me a cigarette.
- I want a cigarette!
- Man, I'm seriously going insane in here.
- Okay, status update.
- Ah, isn't that Take 2's Fukazawa?
- Huh?
- Yeah.
- Ah, well, if we check YouTube we should
know.
- Right, right. - Hello? So, did you
figure out the prime minister thing?
- So, about the prime ministers, we even
had Kotake looking into it, but we still don't know yet.
- Even Kotake?
- It's really hard.
- Ah, then forget it. Forget that one.
- Yeah. - So what happened with the court?
- For the court, Kotake sounds like he can
go for us.
- Oh, Kotake'll go?
- Oh, amazing.
- Yeah.
- That's so nice.
- Kotake's going for us.
- Yeah.
- So what happened with the quiz?
- For the quiz, we've got Kotake too.
- And Sandal's So.
- They're going for us?
- Who is?
- Sandal.
- And, uh, one more thing okay?
- Yeah. - The Take 2 one.
- Are we okay on phone-card units?
- Fukazawa.
- Name the highest mountain Take 2's
Fukazawa has climbed on his YouTube channel.
- He climbs mountains, right? We can
probably find it if we look.
- On YouTube.
- YouTube, right.
- Yeah.
- It'll be a pain if he climbed someplace
really weird. - Yeah.
- Do you know Hata's number, and So from
Sandal?
- I do.
I know, but I forgot to mention one thing.
That Gotanda Queens place only opens at 7
p.m.
- 7 p.m.? Queens?
- Damn.
- Yeah.
- Jeez.
- Well, let's put that aside for now.
- Ah, then for the Sandal guy, uh, tell
Sandal about the TSUTAYA in Nishi-Gotanda.
- Ah, then for the Sandal guy, hurry, the
number, the number.
- Watch the units, the units, the units.
- Ah, So's one.
- Damn, only one left.
- Damn, it's almost over, it's almost
over.
- I'll read So's number. 080-
- Will we make it? 080- Hurry!
- Whoa!
- This is bad!
- It's over!
- Whoa!
- Damn, seriously?
- Bad.
- Whoa.
- Look.
- Brutal.
- It keeps climbing.
- That's way too high.
- It keeps doubling, after all.
- Yeah.
- For now we have to buy it.
- Whoa, wait, how much is it now?
- So that makes six... two, four, six,
eight, ninety.
- Yeah.
- Amazing.
- What happened?
- The Moai statue.
- Aren't there more?
- Even the Harumi Nemoto stuff matched up.
- The Harumi Nemoto vibe.
- Honestly, I've played this before, so I
know. There's no point unless you really spend.
- Right.
- Doing it little by little is the most
pointless thing, right?
- Can I just slam in twenty at once?
There's a point to doing it all in one shot.
- Is that really how it works?
- That's exactly how it works.
- If you don't go bam-bam-bam-bam with it,
it's pointless.
- So it's pointless otherwise.
- You're using twenty, okay? Just remember
that.
- Twenty. - We use twenty, then see how
many come out.
- Ah, set that up.
- Then pour them in.
- Want to go for it?
- Wait, look. It doesn't even watch the
top properly.
- Or what's inside.
- You're stuffing in a lot.
- Quite a lot.
- How about this?
- Yeah.
- Did we use all of this?
- See? That's ten.
- That was ten just now.
- Huh? Huh?
- So how did that last ten feel?
- Isn't this terrifying?
- Don't ask me how it feels.
- That was close, though.
- Close.
- This is bad.
- Shouldn't we stop this?
- Even.
- I don't think these fifty will make it
all the way over here.
- It's hard to build up a reserve in this
game.
- Ah, we got the prime minister one.
- Ah, got the prime minister one? Okay.
- What is it? What about the prime
ministers?
- They all have a kanji numeral in their
names.
- Ah, I see.
- Abe, Koizumi, Obuchi, Miyazawa.
- Right, right, Obuchi, Koizumi. Okay,
thanks.
- And So's phone number is 080-
- 080.
- 080-XXXX-XXXX.
- And tell me Kotake's too, please.
- Uh, 090-
- Okay.
- 090-XXXX-XXXX.
- Okay, okay. So, we still don't know
Fukazawa's yet.
- Fukazawa, from Take 2.
- So Fukazawa... he's got a ton of videos.
- Ah, got it.
- But so far, the highest-looking one
seems to be Mount Norikura.
- Mount Norikura. - He's climbed quite a
bit. - Right, right.
- Right, right.
- Thanks, thanks.
- Fukazawa's YouTube.
- Okay, okay, okay. We can go for the
chance one.
- So that's what it means.
- Okay.
- They all have a kanji numeral in their
names.
- Uh, name the common point among the
former prime ministers.
- Uh, they all have a kanji numeral in
their names.
- How's that?
- Go.
- This is a big one.
- Whoa!
- Oh!
- Good, good, good, good.
- Good, good, good.
- Okay, one more.
- Ah, this can work.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
- Name the highest mountain.
- Uh, so this one is Mount Norikura.
- Mount Norikura.
- Here we go.
- Go.
- Oh!
- Mount Norikura.
- Nice.
- Fukazawa.
- Good, good, good, good.
- It's actually pretty high up.
- Yeah.
- We haven't made any progress.
- Man...
- It still feels like the opening.
- Aren't we getting closer to the ocean?
- No, yeah. I think so.
- Huh? What do we do if the tide comes in?
- Yeah, exactly.
- Wait, isn't this bad?
- It is bad.
- Wait, am I imagining it?
- It's just my imagination, right?
- Wait, isn't the tide actually coming in?
- Isn't it coming in?
- No way.
- Wait a second.
- If it reaches high tide, won't this be
bad in here?
- If the sea comes in...
- Isn't this the kind where we die?
- I've seen this in movies or something.
- The one where people die because of the
rising tide.
- Wait, did they bury us in a safe place?
- Hey.
- Did they?
- Hello.
- Yes.
- Kotake Seigikan?
- Ah, it's Kotake.
- Ah, this is Morita from Saraba.
- Thanks for the help.
- Kotake, uh, the Tokyo Court...
- District Court.
- District, District Court.
Tokyo District Court.
- Right, right.
- So where is it?
- Kasumigaseki.
- So it's in Kasumigaseki.
- Ah, then while you're heading there...
- Okay.
- The Hibiya Park...
- Fountain...
- Tell us today's water temperature.
- The water temperature?
- Right, right, right.
- If you can make it.
- Okay. Uh, is it better before I go?
- Go... ah, after you get there is fine
too.
- Also, by the way...
Kotake, uh, this...
About the court thing,
how long until you know?
- Ninety minutes.
Ninety minutes.
Got it, got it.
Kotake, then in about ninety minutes,
I'll call you back.
- Okay, please do.
- Right, right. Excuse me, then.
- Line up all the dice to one.
- So if they're lined up,
some door opens.
- They're lined up.
- I think I get it.
- Hm?
- This.
- Line them up.
- It doesn't say you have to
roll them into place.
- True.
- Right?
- Just line them up.
- Is that even allowed?
- Huh?
- Ah, I heard something open.
- Huh? What was that?
- I heard something open.
- Huh? Huh? Huh?
- So that's it? No way.
- This.
- Knew it.
- Ah.
- What!?
- Oh.
- Where? What opened?
- What!?
- What opened just now?
- Where is it?
- Nice.
- Whoa.
- Yes!
- I don't know where, though.
- But I definitely heard
something click open.
- We have no idea what opened.
- Ah, open up!
- This crow...
- They were lined up.
That's why it triggered.
- You heard the lock, right?
- What opened?
- Something opened, right?
- What?
- What are you doing?
- Hello.
- Yes.
- So from Sandal?
- Ah, yes.
Uh...
This is Morita from Saraba.
- Ah, good morning.
- Uh, so, I got your number
from Kotetsu of Fire Thunder.
- Right, right.
- Ah, just...
- Not right now, more like
later tonight...
- Huh? You can't head out now?
- It's about a phone call.
- If it's after three...
- No, never mind.
- After three?
- Yes.
- Ah, okay, then at least...
TSUTAYA...
- TSUTAYA, yes.
- The Nishi-Gotanda branch.
- In the 18+ pickup section...
- The adult...
- Yes.
- The pickup section...
- There's a question asking for
the title on the top far-left shelf.
- Oh no, oh no. Twenty-two...
- Yeah.
- If you can, could you go there?
- Uh, right now...?
- Huh? What was that?
- Right now? You mean now?
- You can leave now? Can you make it?
- Ah, I can't move right now.
- You can't? Then forget it.
- Awkward exchange.
- That was a rough back-and-forth.
- Once he can get moving...
- Why'd we even call this guy?
- So it wasn't my imagination.
Isn't it getting way closer?
- No, the sea really is coming in.
- It is. We need to get out of here.
- Hey, OK Google.
What time is high tide?
- High tide is at 3:00 p.m.
- That's pretty soon.
- 3:00 p.m.? What?
- OK Google. What time is it now?
- 12:23.
- Whoa. We've only got three hours.
- Can we make it?
- The waves are really coming in.
- A lot of them are coming in.
- We're actually going to die, aren't we?
- Help! Help! Somebody help!
- Straight to the point.
- Not exactly a DIY approach.
- We're seriously gonna die! Help us!
- Let's save him.
- There's a person buried here!
- Should we go to Thailand?
- At this point, we may have to.
- Yeah, Thailand might be the move.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Ah, Kotetsu?
- Yes.
- It's Morita.
- Ah, good work.
- Good work. So, the capital of
Thailand...
- Yes.
- Can I say it one more time?
- I'll say it from here.
- Ah.
- Krung Thep.
- Yes.
- Wonder if he'll catch on.
- Maha Nakhon...
- Yes.
- Uh, okay...
- Yeah.
- "Mahintara..."
- Huh?
- "Mahintara."
- Wait, "Mahintara."
That's an H sound?
- Yes, definitely an H.
- H? Not an S sound, right?
- Right, it's not.
- Good, good. Mahinta...
- Whoa.
- Not bad. We got it, we got it.
- We got it. We got it.
- Now let's see.
- All right. If we move the big one,
that should finish it.
- We can do it.
- This time for sure.
- I put it before the slope.
- Okay, okay.
- Small "i," small "tsu," then "to."
- That's totally different.
- Right, right. Then what?
- "Sakkathatti..."
- "Ti," right. Yeah, the T sound.
- Yes.
- Yes. "Yawi..."
- Yes. "Yawisanukam..."
- Yeah.
- "Prasit..."
- Prasit. Murasit...
- It's a P sound. - Okay, got it. - Yeah.
- Yes.
- Right, right, right. Thanks, Kotetsu.
I'll call again soon.
- Got it.
- We can do it.
- Oh.
- If this is wrong, I'm crushed.
- Might be it. Might be it.
- You...
- Wait, wait. Okay...
- Phone calls make this hard.
- If this works, that's huge.
- If this works, it's massive.
- At this point we can do it
without another phone card.
- Okay...
- Krung Thep.
- Whoa, let's see.
- Oh, looking good.
- Oh.
- Raya...
- Ah.
- We have to stretch that out.
- Ratchata...
- Ah, it's a long vowel mark.
- I couldn't tell on the long vowel.
- That's a big deal.
- This is where mistakes creep in.
- Awataan...
- So it really was that one here.
- Prasit.
- So it was the long vowel mark.
- Whoa!
- What!?
- This is no good.
- Wrong!
- What do you mean?
- All right!
- Please connect this for real.
- It'll connect.
- Go.
- Here we go.
- Come on.
- Let's go!
- Go!
- Start!
- Please!
- Now what?
- Whoa, this could work.
- It's working, it's working!
- Good, good, good!
- You got this!
- Climb, climb, climb!
- Good, good, good!
- You got this!
- Turn, turn, turn!
- Good, good, good!
- Turn!
- Come on, for real.
- Turn, turn!
- Whoa, it's working!
- You got this!
- Keep it going!
- Oh!
- And...!
- Yes!
- Amazing!
- All right!
- It's moving!
- Yeah!
- It went to the 10-million-yen spot.
- Nice.
- So where is the 10 million?
- We haven't spent any money.
- Right.
- Honestly, just having this here
helps the most.
- No, that was amazing.
- Can't believe you made it there.
- We did it.
- Yay!
- What!?
- Ten million!
- We really did it.
- I'm seriously so happy.
- Then if we move Kai, won't it open?
- Like this.
- The worst possible one.
- We can really get out now.
Finally.
- Ah...
- Yes!
- Move it.
- Pretty...
- I thought this would take longer.
- Let's get out.
- Let's go.
- Good, good, good. - Ten million. - Ten
million.
- Yes.
- Escape.
- Whoa!
- Wait, wait, wait.
- This is bad.
- What is this?
- This is scary.
- Wait a sec.
- No way, seriously.
- We're way up in the air.
- Whoa!
- We're floating, floating!
- We're so high up!
- We're floating!
- Scary, scary, scary!
- This is terrifying!
- What do you mean?
- Wait, wait, wait.
- Where are you sticking that, Omino?
- Wait, wait, the swaying makes
it way scarier.
- How are we supposed to get out?
- Wait a second.
- Ah, I can't reach. - This is bad. -
Whoa!
- This is bad, this is bad.
- This is terrifying.
- Ah, this is scary.
- This is bad. If I move, it's terrifying.
- Scary.
- Wait, this is bad.
- Wait a second.
- What is this?
- So when they said it was swaying,
this is what they meant?
- We're floating.
- Oh no!
- This is scary. Seriously scary!
- Wait, hold on.
- We did open it, but...
- Where even are we?
- Just kill me now!
- [laughs]
- That's a vicious height.
- Incredible.
- For now, that means the C-exit pair...
- Yeah.
- Have technically cleared it.
- Right.
- Though there's probably more after this.
- Huh?
- Why are you closing it?
- I don't want to look. It's scary.
- Scary, scary, scary.
- I mean, I'm scared of heights.
- Oh, I see. - Oh, I see. - Scary, scary,
scary. - Ah, that's what it is.
- Because you could fall.
- It was scary even just opening it.
- It really is scary.
- Yeah.
- This is scary.
- I just assumed it was on the ground.
- Never thought...
- I never thought it would feel this
deadly.
- No, this is incredible.
- Next is the Saraba team.
- Hmm.
- Their helpers are amazing.
They're all really coming through.
- Still, those two from Saraba
are being way too rude.
- [laughs]
- They could show a little more gratitude.
- All of a sudden...
- You get a call from a pay phone telling
you to look up this and that, and if you're slow, they snap at you.
- Even though they're helping them.
- Right, if everyone blocks their number,
it's over. - Exactly. - They're yelling at their helpers. - Kuro-chan might die this season.
- He really might.
- Yeah.
- Sadly, I think Kuro-chan
is done for this time.
- He's gonna die at this rate.
- There's no way in just three hours.
- Yeah.
- There's been zero progress.
- None.
- He's still just calling for help.
- [laughs]
- Exactly.
- He's still trying to solve it
with sheer vocal power.
- He's not even playing along
with the premise yet.